"Hi! How can I help you?"
🎶
Thanks for checking in
I'm not doing well
I'm the new face of management
It's basically hell
There's coffee on my shirt, and burns on my arm
I guess hot oil really hurts a lot!
Working overtime, cuz someone called out
And now we're running out of ice!
Can you tell me how?
To make everything worse
the lights just went dark
Oh, won't you tell me when it's gonna stop?
Please stand back
If you keep yelling, I am gonna have a panic attack!
Please understand
Given the circumstances, I'm doing the very best I can!
mario kart ahh sound effect 🥀🙏
Smile, baby smile for the corporation!
Vital, baby vital to the operation!
Working for an hour costs as much as a sandwich
There's gotta be more than this!
Smile, baby smile through the aggravation!
One day they'll appreciate your dedication!
Never ending orders and I don't have the bandwidth
There's gotta be more than this!
🎶
Thanks for checking in
The shit hit the shit
A lot of money is missin'
from during my shift
There's ringing from the phone
a call from my boss
She said that corporate's gonna call the cops!
When the cops arrived
I figured it out
The totals in the safe were right
I can't fucking count!
I'm desperate to go home
but reading the clock
made me cry hard that I need a mop!
Please look away!
I need a second to reset, today I don't get a break
Please, let me go!
I'm out of sick days so I can't afford to break another bone!
marko kart
Smile, baby smile for the corporation!
Vital, baby vital to the operation!
Working for an hour costs as much as a sandwich
There's gotta be more than this!
Smile, baby smile through the aggravation!
One day they'll appreciate your dedication!
Never ending orders and I don't have the bandwidth
There's gotta be more than this!
🎶
I'm reaching my limit
Red-hot fever, like a sickness
At the maximum, it's pain
and at minimum, it's rage
I'm reaching my limit
Red-hot fever, like a sickness
At the maximum, it's pain
and at minimum, it's rage
that goddamn mcdonalds machine beep noise
I'm not gonna smile!
Fuck the corporation!
Cycle, it's a cycle, not an operation!
All they're ever gonna do is take me for granted!
There's gotta be more than this!
I'm not gonna smile through the aggravation!
They'll never appreciate my dedication!
Never ending orders that I think I'll abandon
There's gotta be more than this!
I know that there's more!
🎶
Yeah